ANNA WEI

SKILLS

SolidWorks experience through designing parts for the Waterloo Rocketry Design Team.

Refined **AutoCAD** skills through development of laser-cut side projects, available on GrabCAD upon request.

Developed mini-projects available on GitHub by coding in C++, Python, HTML, and CSS.

Proficient in **Google SketchUp** and the **Microsoft**Office Suite.

Bilingual in English and Mandarin Chinese.

EDUCATION

University of Waterloo Candidate for Bachelor of Applied Science

September 2018 – June 2023

Mechanical Engineering, Honours, Co-operative Program

Richmond Secondary School Global Perspectives Class of 2018

September 2013 – June 2018

Participant of self-funded humanitarian trip to Tonga. Raised over \$20 000 as a class to support

ACHIEVEMENTS

cause.

Drafting and Design Level II Academic Achievement Award 2016

Utilized AutoCAD and Google SketchUp to design buildings and create a fully rendered, animated walk-through.

Constructed intricate, fully furnished cardboard 3D model of a house project by hand.

CONTACT

anna.wei21@gmail.com

EXPERIENCE

Payload Structure Designer, Waterloo Rocketry Design Team

September 2018 – present

Designed and co-created brace component of CubeSat using SolidWorks by following design constraints and criteria to house an experimental module.

Modelled assortment of screws for SolidWorks rocket payload assembly by following industry-standard dimensions and creating design table of configurations to allow easy access to alternate screw sizes.

Junior Instructor, Geering Up UBC Engineering & Science for Kids

July 2018 - August 2018

Aided instruction of children aged 7-14 by promoting science and engineering topics through hands-on workshops while working with products and programs such as Adafruit and Scratch.

PROJECTS

Edge-Lit Acrylic Arduino Clock

December 2018 – Present

Inspired by the aesthetic of nixie tubes, this project will feature laser-engraved acrylic pieces that display numbers as an Arduino-controlled PCB of multiple LED's is shined through the edges of acrylic.

Laser-Cut Gear Car

December 2-23, 2018

Utilized AutoCAD to create CAD drawings, then laser-cut several prototypes to ensure proper fit of gears and wheel axes.

Finished wooden toy car product featured a figurine which was mobilized by the turning of the wheels on the car.

ACTIVITIES & INTERESTS

Ultimate Frisbee

March 2014 - August 2018

Team Captain

Led team as a captain to the Canadian Ultimate Championships 2017 in Ottawa. Demonstrated leadership and perseverance, as well as ability to help team maintain a positive attitude and high morale.

Team Manager

Directed, organized, and oversaw several fundraisers. Working as a team, was able to fundraise over \$3 000 over two weeks.

Richmond Secondary School Science Team

January 2018 - June 2018

Competed at UBC Physics Olympics 2018. Collaborated with teammates to build and test baking-soda and vinegar powered launcher for the competition.

Awarded with Silver Medal in the Polarization Lab Activity